Office of Publications Records UA012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject Files, 1930 -- 2008; UA012.004; 9.9 Linear Feet; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - Bernstein AV Center, 1984; UA012.004.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Big Brother/big Sister, 1987; UA012.004.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - Biochemistry-Research, 1980 -- 1990; UA012.004.014.00023 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic prints, negatives, brochure manuscript. Date is approximate
  - Biotech, 1990 -- 1995; UA012.004.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - Black History Month, 1987 -- 1997; UA012.004.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - Bookstore, 1983 -- 1991; UA012.004.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - Brass Ensemble, 1985; UA012.004.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - BSOT (1 of 3), 1985 -- 1995; UA012.004.014.00028 (Box 14)
    Contains slides
  - BSOT (2 of 3), 1984 -- 1995; UA012.004.014.00029 (Box 14)
    Contains slides, photographic prints, negatives
  - BSOT (3 of 3), 1983 -- 1984; UA012.004.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Campaign, 1987; UA012.004.014.00031 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic prints (Babbitt compaign)
  - Campaign Galas, 1987; UA012.004.014.00032 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic slide pages. Date is approximate
  - Career Night, 1987 -- 1993; UA012.004.014.00033 (Box 14)
  - Career Fair, 1985; UA012.004.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - Ctr. for Environmental Management, 1986 -- 1991; UA012.004.014.00035 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic prints, Abestos removal negatives (3/85)
  - Photographs, center for Environmental Mgmt., 1984 -- 1990; UA012.004.014.00036 (Box 14)
  - Photographs, Chaplaining, 1983 -- 1998; UA012.004.014.00037 (Box 14)
  - Centa, 1994 -- 1995; UA012.004.014.00038 (Box 14)
  - Chemistry, 1984 -- 1998; UA012.004.014.00039 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic prints, slides, papers (experiment results)
  - Commencement, 1986 -- 1993; UA012.004.014.00040 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1990; UA012.004.014.00041 (Box 14)
  - Photographs, Commencement, 1984 -- 1994; UA012.004.014.00042 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1985; UA012.004.014.00043 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1986; UA012.004.014.00044 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1987; UA012.004.014.00045 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1988; UA012.004.014.00046 (Box 14)
  - Commencement, 1989; UA012.004.014.00047 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic prints, slides
  - Commencement, 1990; UA012.004.014.00048 (Box 14)
    Contains photographic prints, slides, program
  - Commencement, 1991; UA012.004.015.00001 (Box 15)
    Contains photographic prints, slides, papers/speeches/programs
  - Commencement, 1992; UA012.004.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 1993; UA012.004.015.00003 (Box 15)
    Contains photographic prints, papers/speeches/programs
  - Commencement, 1994; UA012.004.015.00004 (Box 15)
    Contains papers/speeches
  - Commencement, 1994; UA012.004.015.00005 (Box 15)
    Contains papers/speeches/programs, photographic prints
  - Commencement, 1995; UA012.004.015.00006 (Box 15)
    Contains papers/speeches/programs, photographic prints, slides
  - Commencement (1 of 2), 1996; UA012.004.015.00007 (Box 15)
    Contains papers/speeches/programs, photographic prints, folder
  - Commencement (2 of 2), 1996; UA012.004.015.00008 (Box 15)
    Contains papers/speeches/programs, folder
  - Commencement (1 of 2), 1997; UA012.004.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - Commencement (2 of 2), 1997; UA012.004.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 1997; UA012.004.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - Commencement (1 of 2), 1998; UA012.004.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Commencement (2 of 2), 1998; UA012.004.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 1998; UA012.004.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 2002; UA012.004.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, 2002; UA012.004.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, Medical Commencement, 2002; UA012.004.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, Medical Commencement, 2002; UA012.004.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Commencement, Medical Commencement, 2002; UA012.004.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Medical Commencement, 2002; UA012.004.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - Commencement - Robing Room, 2002; UA012.004.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - Commencement - Robing Room, 2002; UA012.004.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Commencement - Robing Room, 2002; UA012.004.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Commencement - Robing Room, 2002; UA012.004.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Community Health [red], 1995; UA012.004.016.00005 (Box 16)
    Contains slides. Date is approximate
  - Computers, 1981 -- 1990; UA012.004.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - Crew [green], 1985 -- 1995; UA012.004.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Dance, 1980 -- 1985; UA012.004.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - Dental Alums, 1985 -- 1996; UA012.004.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Dental Dentists with patients [green], 1986; UA012.004.016.00010 (Box 16)
    Contains slides and negatives. Date is approximate
  - Dental in class [green], 1989; UA012.004.016.00011 (Box 16)
    Contains slides, photographic prints and negatives. Date is approximate
  - Dental-Intl. Student, 1997; UA012.004.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Dental mis. [green], 1985 -- 1998; UA012.004.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Dental School, 1980; UA012.004.016.00014 (Box 16)
    Contains transparent prints, negatives. Date is approximate
  - Dental School buildings [green], 1987 -- 1998; UA012.004.016.00015 (Box 16)
    Contains slides, photographic prints
  - Dental School, Dentists with patients [green], 1995; UA012.004.016.00016 (Box 16)
    Contains photographic prints, negatives, photographic transparencies. Date is approximate
  - Dental School, research and equipment [green], 1995; UA012.004.016.00017 (Box 16)
    Contains photographic prints, negatives, slides. Date is approximate
  - Dental School, students in class [green], 1993 -- 1996; UA012.004.016.00018 (Box 16)
    Contains photographic prints, negatives, slides.
  - Dewick/MacPhie, 1995; UA012.004.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - DiBiaggio Chair, 2002; UA012.004.016.00020 (Box 16)
    Contains programs
  - Dining, 1980 -- 1989; UA012.004.016.00021 (Box 16)
  - Dorm Life, 1980; UA012.004.016.00022 (Box 16)
  - Drama, 1983; UA012.004.016.00023 (Box 16)
  - Drama/Dance [green], 1977 -- 1985; UA012.004.016.00024 (Box 16)
  - Edward R. Murrow Center Events, 1954 -- 1975; UA012.004.016.00025 (Box 16)
  - Electro-Optics Technology Center, 1970; UA012.004.016.00026 (Box 16)
    Contains photographic prints, paper. Date is approximate
  - Eliot-Pearson, 1973 -- 1999; UA012.004.016.00027 (Box 16)
  - Diversity Forum 1999, UA012.004.016.00028 (Box 16)
  - Eliot Pearson, 1988; UA012.004.016.00029 (Box 16)
  - Eliot Pearson - Children, 1995; UA012.004.016.00030 (Box 16)
  - Engineering, 1983 -- 1984; UA012.004.016.00031 (Box 16)
  - Engineering, 1980 -- 1993; UA012.004.016.00032 (Box 16)
    Contains photographic prints, negatives, trasparencies. Date is approximate
  - Engineering [teal], 1987 -- 1996; UA012.004.016.00033 (Box 16)
    Contains photographic print, slides.
  - Engineering c. 1988-1995 (1 of 2), UA012.004.016.00034 (Box 16)
  - Engineering c. 1988-1995 (2 of 2), UA012.004.016.00035 (Box 16)
  - Engineering biomechanics lab [teal], 1985; UA012.004.016.00036 (Box 16)
  - Engineering classes (Professors with students) [teal], 1983 -- 1987; UA012.004.016.00037 (Box 16)
    Contains photographic slides
  - Engineering design, 1990; UA012.004.016.00038 (Box 16)
  - Engineering interesting equipment [teal], 1984 -- 1989; UA012.004.016.00039 (Box 16)
  - Engineering interesting people shots [teal], 1986 -- 1996; UA012.004.016.00040 (Box 16)
  - Engineering (music, graphics, environment), 1995; UA012.004.016.00041 (Box 16)
  - Environmental studies, 1995 -- 1996; UA012.004.016.00042 (Box 16)
    Contains photographic prints, Tufts Journal.
  - EPIIC/Ex-College [green], 1997 -- 1999; UA012.004.016.00043 (Box 16)
    Contains photographic prints, bound photo-book
  - Equestrian Team [green], 1990; UA012.004.016.00044 (Box 16)
  - European Cities [teal], 1993 -- 1996; UA012.004.016.00045 (Box 16)
    Contains photographic prints, slides.
  - Fine Arts/Music, 1980 -- 1998; UA012.004.017.00001 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints and slides of art & music at Tufts; includes picture of Orchestra, Jazz band, Jester Hairston, Amalgamates, slides of drama productions, choir, dance, and studio art classes.
  - Photographs, fine arts, 1967 -- 1989; UA012.004.017.00002 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic printsand internegatives of fine arts at Tufts; including dance, drawing, painting, sculpture, and ceramics.
  - Photofile: Fletcher-donors, 1997 -- 1998; UA012.004.017.00003 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints of Fletcher donor event, including photograph of Dean John Galvin and David Powell.
  - Fletcher professors in action, 1982 -- 1999; UA012.004.017.00004 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic slides and film strips.
  - Fletcher School, 1977 -- 1997; UA012.004.017.00005 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints and negatives of Fletcher School faculty, staff, students, honorary degree recipients and commencement speakers. Also includes folder labeled "Fletcher 50th"
  - Fletcher 2, 1977 -- 1992; UA012.004.017.00006 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints of Fletcher School faculty, staff, students, student-run radio program, honorary degree recipients and commencement speakers. Also includes folder labeled "Fletcher 50th"
  - Fletcher students in class, 1987 -- 1996; UA012.004.017.00007 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints, film strips and slides of Fletcher School faculty, staff, students, including photographs of spanish class, music engineering, and afro-american history class.
  - Photofile: Fletcher School (2 of 2), 1980 -- 2002; UA012.004.017.00008 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints, negatives, and internegatives of Fletcher School facilities (Cabot Center), buildings, faculty, staff, and students as well as special events, commencement, and awards ceremonies. Also includes a copy of the 2003 Annual Report, and a program from Viktor Orban's Honorary Degree Ceremony in 2002.
  - Football, 1980 -- 1991; UA012.004.017.00009 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints and slides of football games. Dates are approximate.
  - France - cave paintings misc., 1985; UA012.004.017.00010 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic slides. Date is approximate.
  - Freshman Explorations Program, 1990; UA012.004.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Genetics, 1997; UA012.004.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - Gordon Institute, 1994 -- 1995; UA012.004.017.00013 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints of Gordon Institute Open House (1994), and professors Ken Carr and Ed Aqua.
  - Photographs, Gordon Institute, 1998; UA012.004.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - Graphic elements, 1983 -- 1994; UA012.004.017.00015 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints and slides of books, notebooks, moon, candles, and motherboards.
  - Greek trip [booklet], 1995; UA012.004.017.00016 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints removed from a bound booklet. Date is approximate.
  - Gulf War, 1990 -- 1992; UA012.004.017.00017 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints, slides, and internegatives of Medical School Alumni in Iraq, as well as Tufts teach-ins and anti-war rallies.
  - Health Services, 1990; UA012.004.017.00018 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic slide of health services building.
  - Hellenic Studies, 1998; UA012.004.017.00019 (Box 17)
    Contains brochure for the Center for Hellenic and Southeastern European Studies, a list of Greek correspondents in the US, and a New Bureau release announcing the creation of the Center.
  - Higher Ed Initiative, 1998; UA012.004.017.00020 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints and newspaper clippings from 1998 Higher Ed Initiative (HEI) Symposium.
  - Hillside School Apartments Open House, 2003; UA012.004.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - Jumbofest, 1993; UA012.004.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - Laboratories, 1944 -- 1982; UA012.004.017.00023 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints and negatives of students working in Tufts labs. Also contains a photograph of Charlotte Taylor Davis, Tufts first female graduate to earn a degree in chemical engineering.
  - Photographs, language lab, 1980 -- 1987; UA012.004.017.00024 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints and internegative.
  - Photofile: Lectures, 1987 -- 1990; UA012.004.017.00025 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints of people who came to lecture at Tufts University. Includes photographs of Stuart Saunders, Dr. Eric R. Kandel, Dr. Robert Gale, Gov. Michael Dukakis, and Bill Stanton.
  - Matriculation, 1985 -- 1986; UA012.004.017.00026 (Box 17)
    Photographs of ceremony and students moving in.
  - Matriculation, 1987; UA012.004.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - Matriculation, 1988; UA012.004.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - Matriculation, 1989; UA012.004.017.00029 (Box 17)
    Photographs and negatives of ceremony and students moving in. Also contains newspaper clipping.
  - Matriculation, 1990; UA012.004.017.00030 (Box 17)
  - Matriculation, 1991; UA012.004.017.00031 (Box 17)
  - Matriculation, 1992; UA012.004.017.00032 (Box 17)
  - Matriculation, 1993; UA012.004.017.00033 (Box 17)
  - Matriculation, 1994; UA012.004.017.00034 (Box 17)
  - Matriculation, 1995; UA012.004.017.00035 (Box 17)
    Photographic prints and slides of ceremony and students moving in.
  - Matriculation, 1996; UA012.004.017.00036 (Box 17)
    Photographic prints of ceremony and students moving in.
  - Matriculation, 1997; UA012.004.017.00037 (Box 17)
  - Matriculation, 1998; UA012.004.017.00038 (Box 17)
  - Matriculation / orientation - moving in, 1993 -- 2004; UA012.004.017.00039 (Box 17)
    Photographic slides, prints, and negatives of ceremony and students moving in.
  - MBTA train stops, 1977 -- 1986; UA012.004.017.00040 (Box 17)
    Photographs of Davis station and Tufts University station on commuter rail.
  - Medical board of trustees, 1996 -- 2002; UA012.004.017.00041 (Box 17)
    Photographic prints, slides, and film strips. Also contains slides of Jaharis Center building.
  - Medical docs with patients, 1990; UA012.004.017.00042 (Box 17)
    Photographic film strips and slides. Date is approximate.
  - Medical equipment, 1990 -- 1993; UA012.004.017.00043 (Box 17)
  - Medical Papamarkou fellows, 2002; UA012.004.017.00044 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic slides and brochure regarding Alexander Papamarkou medical scholarship & fellowship fund.
  - Medical photos [1 of 2], 1993 -- 1998; UA012.004.017.00045 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints, slides and negatives of medical alumni from publications.
  - Medical photos [2 of 2], 1992 -- 1998; UA012.004.017.00046 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic prints of medical students and faculty.
  - Medical research, 1997; UA012.004.017.00047 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic slides. Date is approximate. This folder originally contained a CD labeled TUSM: Confocal images, these images were determined to have no archival value, and the CD was removed from the collection.
  - Medical school misc., 1986 -- 1997; UA012.004.017.00048 (Box 17)
    Contains photographic slides and prints. Date is approximate.
  - Medical students in class, 1995; UA012.004.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Medical students in class, 1986 -- 2002; UA012.004.018.00002 (Box 18)
    The majority of this folder is photographic slides, but also contains some prints and prints of negative-sized strips.
  - Medical students (posed), 1995 -- 1996; UA012.004.018.00003 (Box 18)
    contains slides from a 95-96 admissions photoshoot.
  - Medical students - Richard Howard, 2002; UA012.004.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - Medical students studying 1, 1990; UA012.004.018.00005 (Box 18)
    Contains slides and photographic prints. Also contains images of medical library.
  - Medical students studying 2, 1990; UA012.004.018.00006 (Box 18)
    Contains slides and photographic prints. Date is approximate.
  - Medical students studying - R. Howard, 2002; UA012.004.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - Photofile - Medical School surgery, 1986 -- 1990; UA012.004.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - Medical - surgery, 1999; UA012.004.018.00009 (Box 18)
    Includes images of Dean Jones performing surgery.
  - Medical white coat ceremony, 2001; UA012.004.018.00010 (Box 18)
    Includes images of Dean Jones performing surgery. DM.
    - Medical white coat ceremony image cd, 2001; UA012.004.018.00010.00001; Malitsky, Ed
  - Medicine, 1980 -- 1990; UA012.004.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - Photofile - MFA, 1998; UA012.004.018.00012 (Box 18)
    Contains photographic prints and slides of Museum School faculty, staff and students. Including pictures of Deans Debby Dluhy and Bruce McDonald.
  - Photofile - Microelectronics center, 1986; UA012.004.018.00013 (Box 18)
    Not of Center, but of men at the opening.
  - Molecular biology, 1980 -- 1987; UA012.004.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - Molecular and microbiology, 1998; UA012.004.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - Museum School [MFA] students, 2002; UA012.004.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - Museum Studies 98, 1997; UA012.004.018.00017 (Box 18)
    Contains slides, graphic cutouts and pamphlets from museums.
  - Music, 1977 -- 1979; UA012.004.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - Photographs, musical performances, 1985 -- 1993; UA012.004.018.00019 (Box 18)
    Contains photographs and internegatives.
  - NEBH, 1986; UA012.004.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - Photofile - Alice Neel, 1998; UA012.004.018.00021 (Box 18)
    Contains photographic slides of Alice Neel paintings.
  - New England Environmental Conference, 1993; UA012.004.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - New England Environmental Conference, 1990; UA012.004.018.00023 (Box 18)
    Contains program and photographs.
  - Photofile - New England Medical Center, 1997; UA012.004.018.00024 (Box 18)
    Contains newsletter and photograph.
  - Photofile - North Hall, 1972; UA012.004.018.00025 (Box 18)
    Contains photographs of 1972 North Hall fire.
  - Nutrition, 1987; UA012.004.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - Nutrition - Africa, 1985 -- 1997; UA012.004.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - Nutrition buildings - Medford, Boston, 1983 -- 1997; UA012.004.018.00028 (Box 18)
    Contains photographic slides and prints of HRNC and Posner Hall,
  - Nutrition commencement, 1995; UA012.004.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - Nutrition docs with patients, 1987 -- 1998; UA012.004.018.00030 (Box 18)
    Contains photographic slides and prints.
  - Nutrition international, 2000; UA012.004.018.00031 (Box 18)
    - Nutrition international photo cd, 2000; UA012.004.018.00031.00001
  - Nutrition international, 1997; UA012.004.018.00032 (Box 18)
  - Nutrition students in class, 1986 -- 1998; UA012.004.018.00033 (Box 18)
    Contains photographic slides, negatives and prints.
  - Nutrition students (posed), 1997; UA012.004.018.00034 (Box 18)
  - OKU Presentation, 1988; UA012.004.018.00035 (Box 18)
  - Photofile: Olin Language Center, 1990 -- 1994; UA012.004.018.00036 (Box 18)
  - Photofile: Oxfam Cafe, 2000; UA012.004.018.00037 (Box 18)
  - Parents, 1984 -- 1988; UA012.004.018.00038 (Box 18)
    Pictures of Family Weekend and students moving in.
  - Paris, 1984 -- 1988; UA012.004.018.00039 (Box 18)
    Slides and internegatives of Paris landscapes and students sightseeing.
  - Photographs, phonathon, 1990 -- 1993; UA012.004.018.00041 (Box 18)
  - President's Ball 1988, UA012.004.018.00042 (Box 18)
  - Police / safety, 1995; UA012.004.018.00043 (Box 18)
    Photographic slides and prints.
  - Porter, John - HD, 1997; UA012.004.018.00044 (Box 18)
    Programs and photographs from John Edward Porter's receipt of an Honorary Degree from Tufts University.
  - Post Bac 1999+1998 workshops, 1998 -- 1999; UA012.004.019.00001 (Box 19)
    Contains photographs of the event
  - Posters and Signs, 1983 -- 1990; UA012.004.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - Pres. Investigators Award, 1987; UA012.004.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - President's Conf., 1980; UA012.004.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - President's Party, 1980; UA012.004.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - Psychology [yellow], 2000; UA012.004.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Photographs, Public Safety, n.d., 1988 -- 1990; UA012.004.019.00007 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints and transparencies.
  - Public Service, 1991 -- 1997; UA012.004.019.00008 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, program, newspaper clippings.
  - Racism, 1987; UA012.004.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - Photographs, receptions, n.d., 1990 -- 1998; UA012.004.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Refusniks, 1980; UA012.004.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Rehabilitation Engineering Center, 1983 -- 1986; UA012.004.019.00012 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, photocopies
  - Sackler, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.004.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - Sackler immunology [blue], 1986; UA012.004.019.00014 (Box 19)
    Contains slides, photographic prints, reel page. Date is approximate
  - Sackler labs [green], 2002; UA012.004.019.00015 (Box 19)
    Contains slides, photographic prints, reel page.
  - Sackler neuroscience [blue], 1986; UA012.004.019.00016 (Box 19)
    Contains slide, photographic prints, reel pages. Date is approximate
  - Sackler pharmacology [blue], 1990; UA012.004.019.00017 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, reel pages. Date is approximate
  - Sackler photos [old] (1 of 3), 1990; UA012.004.019.00018 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, transparencies, negatives. Date is approximate
  - Sackler photos [old] (2 of 3), 1986 -- 1994; UA012.004.019.00019 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, transparency/negative.
  - Sackler photos [old] (3 of 3), 1982 -- 1992; UA012.004.019.00020 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, reel print pages.
  - Sackler School misc [blue], 1986; UA012.004.019.00021 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, reel print pages, CD, negatives, transparencies. Date is approximate
  - Sci-Tech center, 1990; UA012.004.019.00022 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, reel print pages
  - Soccer [green], 1981 -- 1998; UA012.004.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - Softball [green], 1988 -- 1989; UA012.004.019.00024 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints. (Also contains baseball photographs)
  - Spring Fling, 1985 -- 1991; UA012.004.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - Sports/fitness [green], 1985 -- 1989; UA012.004.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - Sports misc [green], 1986 -- 1992; UA012.004.019.00027 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, slides, negatives, reel print page
  - Stearns Estate, 1987; UA012.004.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - Summer School, 1986; UA012.004.019.00029 (Box 19)
  - Summer School, 1987 -- 1995; UA012.004.019.00030 (Box 19)
  - Summer School, 1986 -- 1995; UA012.004.019.00031 (Box 19)
  - Summer Institute Graduation (English Language Program), 1995; UA012.004.019.00032 (Box 19)
  - Talloires, 1980; UA012.004.019.00033 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, brochure, papers. Date is approximate
  - Talloires [green], 1988; UA012.004.019.00034 (Box 19)
  - Talloires city and regional [teal], 1983 -- 1995; UA012.004.019.00035 (Box 19)
    Contains slides.
  - Talloires landscapes [teal], 1986 -- 2002; UA012.004.019.00036 (Box 19)
    Contains slides, photographs, zip disc
  - Talloires priory [teal], 1983 -- 1994; UA012.004.019.00037 (Box 19)
    Contains slides, photographs, cards
  - Talloires students [green], 1988 -- 1990; UA012.004.019.00038 (Box 19)
    Contains slides, photographs
  - Talloires students [teal], 1984 -- 1992; UA012.004.019.00039 (Box 19)
  - Telefund, 1994; UA012.004.019.00040 (Box 19)
  - Teli, 1993; UA012.004.019.00041 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, newspaper
  - Tuftonia's Day, 1985 -- 1993; UA012.004.019.00042 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, note, reel print page
  - Tuftonia Day, 1985; UA012.004.019.00043 (Box 19)
    Contains photographic prints, negatives, archival transparencies
  - Tufts Alumni Assoc., 1990; UA012.004.019.00044 (Box 19)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990; UA012.004.019.00045 (Box 19)
  - Adults on Campus conference, 1996; UA012.004.020.00001 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of computer lab
  - Adults on Campus conference, 1996; UA012.004.020.00002 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of computer lab, architecture class, woman on playground/near sculpture
  - Africana Center at Capen, 1990; UA012.004.020.00003 (Box 20)